再一次
One more.
好的 那这样呢 先生
-Okay. How's that, sir?
宛如他娘的水晶玻璃鞋  -好的稍等下
Like a glass fucking slipper. Okay, good. Hold on, hold on.
我扶着你
Let me get you...
好 准备好了
There we go. Like that.
我可能需要撒个尿
I think I might need a piss.
你想要上楼吗 别又像上次!
Wanna go back up? -You don't want another...
不 不 不用了 继续走吧
-No... let's get on with it.
我自己能行
I can do it.
"欢迎莅临  股东大会"
"PGN电视台"
"欢迎莅临股东大会"
"威斯达 伊科  年度股东大会"
"总统能力备受质疑"
苏菲 发生什么了 小甜饼
Soph? What's going on, wild honeypie?
你好
Hi.
比安卡不让我喂一小块百吉饼给兔兔
Bianca won't let me feed Megathump a piece of my bagel,
所以..   -好...让比安卡接电话
so... Okay. Put... Bianca on.
给你   -你好
What...  Hi.
你说
Yeah.
我上网查过了 兔子不能吃百吉饼
I looked it up and rabbits aren't supposed to eat bagels.
是这样的 比安卡
Okay. Bianca?
让那只兔子吃百吉饼
Let the rabbit have some bagel.
那些规矩是说给坦帕大学的蠢蛋听的
Those rules are for fuckheads who are gonna go to Tampa
他们只会喂兔子喝"重量杯"[7-11贩售的便宜饮料]
and leave a rabbit with a Big Gulp
和一打肉桂葡萄干
and a dozen cinnamon raisin.
吃一个...一点百吉饼不会死的 好吗
A little's not gonna hurt, yeah?
今日的头条新闻理所当然是.
Our top story this morning is of course...
先这样 谢谢 再见苏菲
Okay, thanks. Bye, Soph.
..传媒巨鳄韦斯达·罗伊科的命运
...the fate of media giant Waystar Royco hangs
悬而未决
in the balance.
独到的见解啊史蒂夫   -这家传媒巨鳄的
-Great insights, dude. -The 50th anniversary
五十周年纪念日被证实为...
of the media giant is proved...
好了影子作战间
Okay. Shadow Chamber.
#反抗#的总部
HQ of the hashtag resistance.
怎么样 大家还好吗
What up? How are we feeling?
准备好战斗了宝贝 没错
-Rise and grind, baby. -Hell yeah.
董事长洛根·罗伊和梅斯贝里资本
...between founder chairman Logan Roy...
他还有多久会抵达   -你爸在路上了
-What's his ETA? -Your dad's en route.
之间的代理权争夺战目前势均力敌
...Capital banner is currently "too close to call".
双方已花费近一亿美元
The sides have spent close to $100 million
来赢取各个公司投资人和股东们的
fighting a battle to win the hearts, minds, and votes
青和选票
of corporate investors and small shareholders.
分组名单在桌上   -各方立场毫无松动
-Group on the table. -Positions are entrenched
因此股东们的选票至关重要
so it's down to the shareholders to decide
我们会及时报道结果
-and we'll bring you the outcome...
行了 闭嘴吧 史蒂夫·考克斯
-All right. -Shut up, Steve Cox. -...
以及所有反馈
and all the reaction as soon as it comes in.
你让我紧张了 老家伙
Yo, yo, are you sweating me on Golden Pond?
我们究竟达成协议了没
Have we got a deal or what?
肯 我得私下告诉你
Ken, I would privately like to transmit
我有一丝不安
a certain degree of trepidation.
他来了 膳操心大师 和被他汗水浸湿的意大利面
There he is. The Panic Meister cooking up his sweaty spaghetti.
你今天葫芦里卖的又是什么药 弗兰克
So what... what bullshit are you selling me today, Frank?
我们还未取得突破
We haven't had a breakthrough
而洛根势必会采取投票表决
and Logan is definitely willing to let this go to a vote.
他不会毁了这一切吧
He's not gonna fuck this, is he?
我只是在想 如果有必要
I'm just thinking, if we need it,
我们是否该留个秘密交流通道
is there a back channel here?
让莫斯科的人知道华盛顿的人在想什么
It might be nice to let...Moscow know
也许是件好事
what Washington's thinking today
以免咱们意外触发了世界末日
so we don't all stumble into Armageddon?
好 那..那就保持通道畅通
Yeah. Let's... let's keep this channel open.
鹰巢完毕
Eagle's Aerie out.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 5 集
凯莉 你今天坐前排好吗
Will you sit out front today, Kerry?
我要知道这些看戏的人在想什么
I need to know what the temperature is among the shit-munchers.
好的 这样的话 我要把这些交给你
Sure. In that case, I'm gonna leave you with these, yeah?
好的 不用提醒   -你会记得吧
-Oh, yeah. No, no. -You'll remember?
你不需要我...好的 我自己可以的
-You don't want me to... -Yeah, I've got it covered.
操
fuck.
他们到哪了
Where are they?
好 他们来了
Okay. Here they come.
和桑迪斯图伊他们谈得如何
So? How are Sandy and Stewy?
我们的情况是什么
How we looking?
你们怎么搞砸的
How'd you fuck it up?
整个谈崩了 他们想要的我们给不了
Total breakdown. They wanted the moon on a stick.
连续两天搞到凌晨五点
Two 5.00am nights.
如果局面失控了
If we lose control,
直接把我喊醒 然后告诉我 我的职业生涯到此结束 好吗
just wake me up to tell me my career's over, okay?
操那.
Oh, fuck. Was...
有谈好任何一项协议吗
was there a deal there?
我不知道
I don't know.
对方毫无妥协
No concessions.
他们要四个董事会席位
And I mean four board seats?
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous!
肥肉都给他们拿走 只留骨头给我们
What... It's full fat for them and...corndogs and toenails for us.
我认为 最终要和解的话
I think, at the end of the day, to settle
桑迪想要看到的是
the clause Sandy really wants
洛根·罗伊从此以后坐在开瓶器上旋转
is that Logan Roy henceforth sits on a corkscrew and spins.
对   -这点我们办不到
-Yeah. -Hard to give that.
好吧 那我们只能投票
Okay. Well, then we're down to a vote.
咱们要上同一艘船了
-We're climbing into the vote boat.
好极了 投票
-Great. Voting.
咱们就把决定权丢给爱达荷州的退休保洁吧
Let's just throw it open to the fucking retired janitors of Idaho.
玛雅  情况如何了
Maya? Where are we?
不相上下
Too close to call.
有些股东要等你父亲演讲后再投票
Some shareholders won't vote till they hear your father, so.
只要上帝开口 那些孬种就无处可逃
Well, those pussies aren't gonna bail once they hear God speak.
我们要失去公司了
We're gonna lose the company.
今天我们就要失去这操蛋的公司了
We're gonna lose the fucking company today.
不不  -如果乔希·阿伦森反对的话
-Nope. -If Josh Aaronson is against
你们很难以明显的优势
it is hard to see how you win this
赢得这场票选
with a clear margin.
我们花钱请代理律师小组 就这吗
Is this what we pay the proxy solicitor team for?
如果我给格雷格五百万美元
You know, if I were to give Greg five million
他也会说“情况很糟
he'd say, "Ooh, it looks bad," you know?
我来了 顺利抵达   -援兵来了
-Hey! -The cavalry has arrived. -Here I am. I made it.
太好了 你的到来是"如此重要
-Great. It's so essential you're here.
谢谢   -最新消息是
-Thanks. -So the news is
明天我们都得在塔吉特旗下的公司
is tomorrow we're all gonna try to look for jobs
找新工作了
in the same branch of Target.
这笑话不错   -当然
-That's funny. -Yeah.
挺好的   -谢谢
-That's good. -Thanks.
老爸在哪  我要谈谈
Where's Pop? I wanna spitball.
改天吧 老康
Yeah, maybe not today, Con?
今天不太适合闲聊  没那时间
Not the best day for a chat? No time.
真倒霉
Oh, bummer.
但我觉得他得挪出时间来  国务卿夫人
I guess he'll have to make time, Madam Secretary.
除非他想让我 向大众曝光
Unless he wants me to go public and take a big,
咱们污迹斑斑的家族事迹
black light to our semen-stained family scrapbook
也许他值得为我花点时间对吗
maybe he ought to fit me in, yeah?
好吧   -我饿了
-Okay. -I'm hungry.
那个猛汉 他来了
Hey. Here he is. The Big Beast.
准备好 用他的超级靴子 痛踢四方了
Ready to kick ass with his big ass-kicking boot.
你听说我们的情况了吗
So, you heard where we're at?
卡尔呢格丽呢
Karl? Gerri?
我觉得 得延迟票选
I guess delay the vote.
挤压桑迪和斯图伊的露脸时间
Squeeze Sandy and Stewy's airtime.
再利用我们的加长版演讲
Run the long versions of the speeches.
我发送了一份股东名单的邮件
I emailed a list of assigned shareholders
为了在最后一刻说服他们
for last-minute persuasion.
很好 很好
Good, good.
好 好的
Okay, yes.
就这样吗
And that's it?
没有其它我们能做的吗
There's nothing else we can do?
老家伙那边呢
What about the Raisin?
白宫气得都快把屋顶掀翻了
Well, the White House is shitting fuel rods
气我们将典论转向
at the tone change.
PGN 在播报“记忆门"「坪击总统是个老糊涂]
PGN is running with Memory Gate
试图让总统公布检查结果
and they're calling for him to release tests.
有很多电话打来 但我们只是简单粗暴的抨击
And there's a lot of calls coming in, but we're sandbagging.
很好 很好 我们得发表个什么
Good. Good. Press for something.
一个声明 关于声明的谣言
A statement, a rumor of a statement.
任何能在票选前 让我们看似赢了的
Anything before the vote that looks like a win
顺带 让司法部那事降温
and turns the temperature of the DOJ down.
很好 虽然为时已晚了
Great. Late in the day,  very late in the day
但 聊胜于无
but potentially, all the more useful.
很好   -很好
-Good. -Good.
进来吧
Yo, yo. Come on in.
请把你的名牌留在门口
Leave your fucking lanyard at the door.
欢迎来到真正的年度大会
Welcome to the real annual meeting.
你好吗伙计  你好吗
-What's up, man? -What's up?
你不是应该站在彩色肥皂盒上
Shouldn't you be on a rainbow soap box somewhere
大喊时间到"了吗
screaming "Time's up"?
对  但掌控不了家族
Right. Yeah. Well, without family control
我就无法做出改变
I can't change things.
这正是我要做的改变
And that's actually what I'm about. Change.
你应该说给"名利场"听   兄弟  不是我
Well, you should save that for Vanity Fair, bro. I'm all good.
随便吧 听着
Whatever. Look,
我今天唯一的目标是
my only agenda today
此时比刻 达成属于咱们的协议
right now, is find a deal that works for both of us.
哦 是吗 扯蛋呢
Cool. Okay. Bullshit.
公司里 我是你最强大的盟友
I'm your most powerful ally in the company.
我知道..
I know
你的财务状况摇摇欲坠
your financing's starting to wobble.
你不想要为了票选孤注一掷
You don't wanna risk everything on the dice roll of a vote
我们也是
any more than we do.
我们要是输了 走掉就好
Well, we lose, we walk.
再把标靶转向其他公司
We just move to the next company.
是吗 你们钱包里已流失了五千万
Yeah? With a $50 million hole in your pocket?
你想要从中获利 桑迪想要打败我爸
You want something out of this. Sandy wants to hurt my dad.
所以 不如水推舟
So let's make this happen.
我爸那边的"内部人士”现在暗示
I got an inside track with my dad right now.
他已经为投票做好百分之百的准备了
He's 100% ready to take this to a vote.
该死的...
Fucking...
那太愚蠢了肯   -斯图伊我知道
-That would be very stupid, Ken. -Stewy, I know you guys
你们一直在争取更好的条件
have been angling for a better deal
也觉得 即使挺而走险也无所谓
and you don't think there's any risk taking this to the brink
但我确定 你们不可能成功
but I know for a fact you're not gonna get one.
他是个变态自恋狂
He's a psychopathic narcissist
他觉得他可以把事情搬上台面
he thinks he can take this to the floor
用他强大的洛根巫术
drag back the undecideds with his...
说服那些犹豫不决的人  大获全胜
beefy Logan voodoo and win outright,
而且你知道的 我很难说 谁知道他能不能呢
and, you know I don't know. Who's to say he can't?
所以 你知道的 伙计.
So, you know, dude, just
回到谈判桌上来 做个交易吧 都准备好了
come back to the table, make a deal, it's there.
然后...
And...
你知道的..
you know,
此刻只需要克服自我障碍
it's... at this point, it's just managing egos.
洛根
Hey, Logan?
是斯图伊·侯赛因打来的
It's Stewy Hosseini.
要接吗
Shall I?
喂 斯图伊怎么了
Hey, Stewy? What's up?
好的 稍等
Okay, hold on.
他们想见个面
They wanna meet.
有些想法要沟通
They have thoughts.
好的 可以 我们参加
Okay. Right. We're on.
有些想法? 什么样的想法
They have thoughts? What kind of thoughts?
他们对议价空间有些想法
They have ideas for a deal space for a settlement.
太他妈棒了   -是的
-fucking A! -Yeah.
那就去吧  -好
-Let's do it. -Okay.
他们为什么突然决定和解
Why have they suddenly decided to settle?
因为他们知道 这是最明智的选择
Well, because they know that it's the smartest move?
或者他们听到了坏消息
Or they've had bad news?
他们掌握了什么我们不知道的情况吗
What do they know that we don't know?
好吧 我们...
Well, let's...
我们去看看好吗   -不行
-let's find out, right? -No.
我不打无准备之仗[跳踢踏舞]
I'm not doing a tap dance.
小西 卡尔 格丽 罗慕路斯 你们去  回来汇报情况
Shiv, Karl, Gerri, Romulus. -Go and report back.
我觉得 这很明智
-I think that's smart.
但 格丽应该上台主持大局
But Gerri should be out front helming,
所以 还是我去吧
so should I go?
我们要重罚你 弗兰克 明白吗
We nail you to the cross, Frank, all right?
好吧
Okay.
好了 我们...
And let's
让桑迪去应对吧「跳软鞋踢踏舞]
let Sandy do the soft shoe.
他在垂死挣扎
He's wriggling.
让我们榨干他们
Let's screw them out.
好的 我会的   -好 你说得对 爸
-Okay. -Okay. You got it, Dad.
妹妹 听着
Sis, hey, listen.
我要给你点甜头
I'm gonna throw you a bone
因为我不希望你记忆中的第一次股东大会
because I don't want you to remember your first shareholder meeting
落下一个输掉公司的结局
as the one where you lost us the company.
所以 无论你们的议价空间是什么
So whatever the deal space you end up in
桑迪都会执意拒绝
Sandy's gonna be too obdurate to say yes.
但别慌
But stay cool
女儿桑蒂有信心能让他和解
daughter Sandi's confident she can get him to settle.
显然她知道怎么操纵她爸
Apparently, she knows how to play her dad.
傀儡大师出场了
Puppet master out.
好了 谢谢 我不想再接到这种电话了
Yeah. Thanks. I no longer wish to receive these calls.
桑迪真的得了梅毒吗
Does Sandy really have syphilis?
如果他全身都是疮 怎么办
What if he has sores all over his body?
如果他的腹股沟被吃光了
What if his groin is all eaten away
上半身掉下来了怎么办
and the top half of him just falls off.
梅毒
Syphilis...
这个谣言好像是我们散布的   -我不知道
-I think we started that rumor. -I don't know.
晚期症状是痴呆 应该是这个
Late-stage symptom is dementia, I believe.
你仓惶的
Yeah, you've been doing some panicky
熬夜上网时查到的吗
late-night googling there, Karl?
你们好  谢谢你们的到来
Hey. Thanks for coming.
桑迪
Sandy.
桑蒂
Sandi.
我父亲很高兴见到你们
My father is very excited to see you all.
那么 听着
So, look.
经过慎重地考虑
After careful consideration
如果我们能在这里达成协议
if we can make a deal here
我们愿意停战
we're willing to agree to a standstill
也就是收购不会进行
so no takeover.
只要我们在未来的交易选择上占领先地位
And provided we lead on deal-making options moving forward
我们将同意继续合并董事长和首席执行官的职位
we'll accede to a continuation of combined chairman and CEO roles
所以那些.. 都是你们的了
so that's... that's all yours.
我觉得这听起来很合理
I think that sounds reasonable.
那三个董事会席位呢   -包括你自己的吗
And the three board seats? Including yours?
我们现在就可以决定
We can do that right now
我爸已经授权了我
I have my Dad's authorization to go there.
你们得到批准了吗
Can we sign off on this?
爸
Dad?
他需要你们承担我们的支出
And he wants our costs covered.
以及有权否决
And veto right over
任何接任首席执行官的罗伊家族成员
any Roy family member ever taking over as CEO.
斯图伊
Stewy?
他是这么说的
That's what the man says.
这对我们来说是非常重要的保障
It is a very important protection for us.
我觉得我有必要说清楚  说一句
I feel like I just have to put it right out there, say it
毕竟这是一个850亿美元的交易
since there's an $85 billion baby on the table here.
我怎么确定 他不是你的傀儡
How do I know that he's not your meat puppet?
我只是按我爸说的做  和你们一样
Oh, I just do what my dad tells me, like you guys.
介意我们休息一下吗   -当然不
Do you mind if we take a beat? Sure.
没错 你们"有的是“时间 不必争分夺秒
Yeah. You have tons of time. Seconds. Whole minutes.
我只是说 他们有的是时间
I'm just saying they got tons of time.
斯图伊   -搞什么名堂
What the fuck?
那啥 除了那个新提案之外
Well, I mean, other than the new proposal
真的已经非常吸引人了
it's a very, very attractive prospect.
抱歉 没什么好谈的
I'm sorry, there's nothing to discuss.
这会置我们于死地 这就是为了羞辱爸
It fucks us and it's designed to humiliate Dad.
对 但它从根本上来说是...
Right. And it's basically optics.
个人看法 毕竟..
I mean,
我都不确定这能不能成立
I'm not sure it would even stand up.
如果真的谈到这个 你应该能绕过去的 对吧
And you could probably work around, right, if it ever came to it?
恕我直言 格丽
With all due respect, Gerri?
翻脸吧
Get bent.
听着 好吧 当然这很丢脸
Look, okay, sure, it's humiliating
但我有99%的把握 你爸会同意的
and I'm 99% certain your dad would agree.
但考虑到我们现在的情况 我得向他汇报一下
But given where we're at, I have to check in with him.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
她要整垮我们吗
Is she gonna fuck us?
什么
What?
不会吧 我不知道
No. I don't know.
你他妈问我干什么 我怎么知道
Why the fuck you're asking me? I don't know.
好 这就是他们想要的 好的
Okay. -What's he... -Yeah.
我们会承担你们的支出 但无法给予否决权
We will meet your costs, but no veto.
我们需要否决权
-We need the veto.
没有替代选项吗
-Is there no alternative shape here?
我们几乎快谈妥了
-We're so close.
快点决定吧 桑蒂  我们都想早日达成协议
-Come on. Sandi we... we all want this to work.
再问问吧
Go in again.
好的
Okay.
我同意 我同意
I agree.
没问题
It's okay.
我们要想一想 但是..但是..
We're gonna go have a think. But...
我们同意...如果..
we do agree it would be a shame if...
因为一个细节而前功尽弃 就太可惜了
if you destroy all this hard work over a detail.
是的没错   -对吧
-Yeah. Right. -Right?
我们移交律师负责吧
Let's let the lawyers get to work.
我们有讨论空间    -就是这样
-We have a landing space here. -There you go.
傻逼豆袋椅   -给您
-fucking beanbag. -Here you go, sir.
好多了
Oh, that's better.
要喝水吗
You want a water?
凯莉说 你需要多喝水
Kerry says you need to stay hydrated.
不喝  -确定不喝吗
-No. -You sure?
嘿 爸爸
Hey, Pa.
有时间吗
Got a minute?
日程很紧 儿子
Tight, son.
晚点吧
Later.
听着 爸
Look, Dad.
我听说 白宫情况动荡
I hear that things are shaky at the White House
但他会再度当选
but he'll win again.
你听到的是这样吧
Is that what you hear?
我想直接请你
I wanted to ask you directly
在公司帮我安排一个重要岗位
for a really significant role within the firm
为我的声誉和前途
to burnish my reputation
镀个金
-for my future.
你以前对这些不感兴趣
-You were never interested.
也许因为以前没人鼓励过我
Well, maybe I was never encouraged?
我不想听陈年旧事
I don't do ancient history.
我也不想谈陈年往事
I don't wanna get into ancient history, either.
所以...
So...
我们能...
can we...
达成共识吗
find common ground?
我只是觉得你没那个金刚钻
I just don't think you have the track record.
罗曼是个傻瓜
Roman's a knucklehead.
小西是个骗子
Shiv's a fake.
肯 人格扭曲
Kenny's screwy.
为什么不能给我个机会   -比如什么
-Why can't I get a shot? -Like what?
欧洲非重要业务
Europe. Nothing vital.
比如
Like...
电视业务
cable?
厕所在哪儿   -这个嘛
Where's the john? Yeah, so,
抱歉 最近的那个厕所坏了
unfortunately, the nearest one is out of order
您需要沿着走廊走到头 上楼 厕所就在您的右手边
you'll have to go down the hall, up the stairs, and on your right.
算你走运 我穿的是运动鞋
Oh, fucking lucky I'm wearing my sneakers, huh?
好梗
Good one.
怎么了
Yeah?
抱歉  -抱歉什么
-Sorry about... -About what?
你想搞翻我  来巩固自己的地位吗
Trying to fuck me over to consolidate your position?
不是
No.
只是 这好像更有利于生意
It just seemed to make business sense.
那就要抛弃我  任我自生自灭吗
Throwing me overboard to drown?
格丽 你已经做出选择了
You picked your prince, Gerri,
别现在站出来说鬼话   -他们需要时间考虑一下但是
don't fuck it up now.
我认为..我们成功了
You know, I think I... we did it.
所以 希望好运吧
So, yeah, fingers crossed.
好的 一会儿见
Okay. See you soon.
你不介意我转告这个消息吧
Oh, you don't mind me relaying the news, do you?
当然 我一点儿都不介意
No, not at all.
毕竟他是我爸 所以.
He's my dad, so.
当然
Yeah.
斯图伊 我感受到了 气氛很对头
Stewy? I'm feeling it. Feeling those good vibrations.
让我看到你是哪一边的 行吗
Let me know where your head's at. Yeah?
咱们把这事搞定 然后一起蹦迪吧
Let's get this done and trip the light fantastic.
你好   -你好
Hey, yeah.
我还在想 你会不会在这
I was wondering if you were gonna be over here.
对 我在这儿
Yeah. I'm... I'm over here,
这是我的工作   -他来了
just doing my job. There he is.
格雷格先生
McGregor.
格狗 今天是重要的一天
Big day, big dog.
是的 所以 兄弟我只是
Yeah. So, hey, man, I just...
我只是想说
I just wanted to say,
我. 我可能.
you know, I'm probably
我相信你可能感觉很失望
I'm sure that you're probably pretty upset
因为我投靠了韦斯达 还有..
over me going to Waystar
我加入了联合辩护   -没关系的
and their Joint Defenses... -No, it's fine.
我..我没得选 真的
-I... I had no choice
因为这关系到..   -是的 我理解
-really, in terms of... -Yeah. I get it.
那就好
Okay.
听你这么说 我真是松了口气 因为.
Wow that's a huge relief. 'Cause...
我外公叫我今天去见他
I've been summoned to see my Gramps today
我觉得
and I just feel like
我不想两头受气 因为...
I don't wanna be getting it -in both ends because...
但是 听我说 我可能得卖了你
-But, look. I may have to burn you.
你..你说什么
You... sorry, what?
对
Yeah.
木已成舟
It is what it is.
我想把你叫过来 给你个客观的警告
I wanted to get you up here and give you fair warning
作为好哥们儿
as a pal.
这样可以吗
That okay?
什么 ... 被出卖吗
What... getting burned?
是的 被出卖
Yeah, getting burned.
这样可以吗..
Is it okay?
听起来很不好
It doesn't sound great.
当然 所以
Yeah. So...
事情是这样的  今天我爸达成了一个交易
here's the thing. My dad lands a deal today
这巩固了他的地位
that strengthens his position.
丽莎说 司法部关于这个案子的态度并不明朗
Lisa says the DOJ is noncommittal about the case
所以  我得给他们点料
so I need to throw them red meat.
我想的是  把你供出来
The thought is I give them you.
不会全盘供出  只是一点点
It's not much, but it's a morsel
而且 也可能是把汤姆或者比尔供出来
plus, it likely gives them Tom, maybe Bill,
你懂的 这样可以施压
you know it builds the pressure,
然后 也许有人会背叛老爸
and then maybe someone flips on Dad.
懂了吗
You see?
兄弟
Dude...
这本不是我的第一选择
It's not my preferred choice.
也不是我的第一选择 我...我以为
Or mine. I... I thought
你说过的 你永远不会卖我
you know, you said you'd never burn me.
我说过 我努力不卖你
-I said I'd try not to burn you. -And...
不是这样的 你说过..
Well, no. You said...
-在飞机上你说过..   -听着
-On the plane, you said... -Hey...
我们别争论“他说了什么 她又说了什么“了
Let's not he said, she said this,
每个人都说过很多话
a lot of shit gets said.
听我说
Look.
我不是说我一定会卖你
I'm still not saying I will burn you.
我只是说 我有可能会卖你
All I'm saying is I might burn you.
不到万不得已
It's a margin call.
那情况到底会有多糟糕呢
And just how bad will the burning be?
其实虽然我在问 但我也知道会很糟...
I mean, even as I ask that, I can tell it's not gonna be...
也许你会没事的
You'll probably be fine.
他们也不想把食物链底端的无名小卒送进监狱
They don't wanna send bottom feeders to prison.
他们可能只是利用你 然后会放过你
They'll probably just fuck you and chuck you
来钓到真正的大鱼
to get to the red meat.
太好了
Great.
或者 你现在就退出联合辩护
Or you drop from the Joint Defense.
肯
Hey, Ken.
我得去看看会议情况了
I have to monitor the meeting,
我只是想事先告知你一声
but I wanted to give you a heads up.
格雷格 我喜欢你这个人
I like you, Greg.
真的喜欢
I really like you.
操
Oh, fuck.
就在这儿   -开大声点好了
-It's up there. -Turn this shit up. All right.
回见
See you.
来啦
Hey...
你好哇 外公
Hey, Gramps?
你最近怎么样
How you doing?
我迟到了一会儿 但是今天肯定很有意思
A little late, but we got an interesting day ahead.
小子 别想给我灌迷魂汤
Don't try to sweet talk me, kiddo.
好的 只是...打个招呼
Okay. Just a few... few words of greeting
但是
but...
皮尤先生 您好
and, hey, Mr. Pugh, how are you?
格雷格 我不是个不谙世事的人 我看出你的小把戏了
I'm not an uncomplicated man, Greg, I know that.
尽管如此 我已经竭尽所能
Nevertheless, I have tried as much as I am able
给你爱和同理心了
to show you love and compassion.
好吧 别逗了
Yeah. Oh, yeah, are you kidding?
你是全世界最好的外公
You're the best darn gramper out
所以 我想要向你..
and I wanted therefore to ask you...
你来找我寻求帮助
You asked me for help.
我认真对待你的请求了
And I took that request seriously.
然而 现在我听说 你放弃了罗杰提供的法律服务
And now I hear that you've dispensed with Roger's services
想必你已决心与我兄弟共命运了
presumably to throw your lot in with my brother
还有他那贪得无厌的诈骗集团
and his gang of crapulous shills
甚至都不打电话通知我一下
without even so much as a telephone call?
是这样的
Right.
我其实在想
I was actually wondering
我也许不该和这里的前辈皮尤先生
if I shouldn't maybe take another turn around the block
拐弯抹角了
with old Mr. Pugh here
我已经认识罗杰·皮尤55年了
I have known Roger Pugh for 55 years.
你他妈的别想着愚弄他
You don't take him for a fucking ride anywhere.
他是我的朋友
-He's a friend of mine!
我...我的意思是
-I mean, I...
好吧 我想另一条路是
Okay. I... I guess the other route
看看是否有其他方法 比如..
is to see if there's any way that
有没有这个可能
you might see your way clear
你给我提供一些经济援助
to providing a little financial support
助我保持一个中立的地位..   -罗杰
to help me retain my neutrality amongst... -Roger.
我正在帮你的外公
I'm helping your grandfather transfer
转移他的全部财产
the entirety of his estate
捐给慈善事业
to charitable endeavors.
什么
What's... what?
格雷格 我要把我所有钱捐给“绿色和平"组织
I'm giving all my money to Greenpeace, Greg.
什么..连我应得的那份也要捐吗
What... Even my part?
第一个捐的就是这部分
That was the first part.
为什么
Why? What?
为什么第一个就要捐我的 你怎么.
Why is that the first part? I mean, how do you...
你怎么分得清啊
how can you tell? I mean...
为什么啊   -因为  格雷格....
-Because... because, Greg... -Why?
你的人生并不是一件小事
...your life is not a bagatelle.
因为你任由自己
Because you are putting yourself
为一群可恶的人做事
in the service of a monstrous endeavor.
因为
Because...
孩子 因为你需要认真对待你的人
Because you need to take yourself seriously, kid.
我们现在该进去了
Now, we should go in.
速战速决
-Okay. So just whip through it. -Right.
尽量最小化异议
Keep any dissent to a minimum.
一旦交易达成 我们会告诉你的
As soon as the deal's agreed, we'll let you know...
然后你就可以宣布投票已经取消了
...and then you can announce that the vote has been called off.
格丽已经发了她的开幕致辞 我们是你坚实的后盾 懂吗
Oh, Ger sent her opening remarks, so we got your back, okay?
好的 好  把他们拿下吧
-Yeah. -Good. Go get 'em.
"年度股东大会"
"大家好,我是格丽凯你曼"
大家好
Hi.
我是副董事长弗兰克·弗农
I'm Frank Vernon, Vice-Chairman.
欢迎参加韦斯达·罗伊科第46 届年度股东大会
Welcome to Waystar Royco's 46th annual shareholders' meeting.
向凯旋归来的英雄们致敬
-All hail the conquering heroes! -Hey!
还没..
It's not a...
老康  交易还没完全敲定
It's not a done deal yet, Con, you know.
但是很接近了
But we're close.
我认为律师可以敲定剩下的细节 对吧
I think the lawyers can finesse the rest, yeah?
是的
Yes.
老爸 你肯定会很高兴
Dad, you would have fucking loved it.
桑迪奄奄一息
Sandy is barely alive.
你甚至可以让他吃自己的纸尿裤
You could have told him to go fucking eat his own diaper
而他只能这样回应
and his only response would be...
就他妈的..
fucking...
等等 什么 你们成功了吗 你们搞定了吗 我们搞定了吗
Wait, what? You did it? We're on?
我们..   -是的
-Well... like... -Yeah.
除此之外 他们已经没有新手腕了
They've got nowhere else to maneuver, so.
他们早就可以答应了
-Wow. -They could have said yes in Greece.
是啊   -省得我们着急半天
-Yeah. -Saved us all the ball-ache.
不过 洛根 这依然是个好消息
-Still. Logan, this is good news.
可不是嘛
-Oh, yeah.
他们的好消息 我们的环消息
Good for them. Bad for us.
爸 这怎么就是坏消息了
Dad, how can it be bad for us?
他们自始至终都会和解
They were always gonna settle.
这里面肯定有什么蹊跷
Oh, something's screwy going on.
我们是不是给了他们对症的解药呢
Do we give them a taste of their own medicine?
要让大家都知道
Let everyone know
他们向我折腰了吗
that they bent for me?
要重启谈判吗 爸
Reopen the negotiation, Dad?
不行吧 我们现在不跟他们和解 就等看被投票出局了
No, we... we settle now or we go to the vote and lose.
告诉他 不准踏进这栋楼半步
Tell him he can't step foot inside the building!
听着 洛根 我知道你很不爽 但是我们必须走这步
Look, Logan, I know how painful this is, but we need this.
我的天 老爸 你刚刚还说
Christ, Dad, you just said
这跟我们最初开的条件差不多
it's not far off what we originally offered.
毁了这笔交易
You know, we fuck this deal,
就再也没有条件可以谈了
and there are no more deals.
怎么样 好吧
Okay.
很好
Great.
好的 谢了 爸爸你很明智
Okay. Thanks, Dad. That's... it's smart.
真的
It is.
你做得很好  -做得很好
-Well done. -Well done.
谢谢   -真的很棒
-Thanks. -Well done.
药
Pills.
抱歉 先生要雅维吗
Sorry, sir. Advil?
你是怎么想的
What do you think?
什么
Sir?
关于这场交易
About the deal?
应该还可以吧
It could be good.
要雅维吗
Get Advil?
我去给你拿点
I'll get some Advil.
我还想请一个人上台  理查德
I would also like to invite to the stage, Richard...
倒霉蛋 弗兰克
fucking Frank.
太丢人了
It's humiliating.
都那么多年了 他还在扮演
All these years, he still has to play
瞎吹牛酒店领班的角色
maitre'd at the Bistro of Bullshit.
喂 怎么了 我这边还没结束
Yeah, what? I'm in the middle.
罗伊先生 很抱歉打扰您 您的兔子生病了
Mr. Roy, I'm sorry to bother you, but the rabbit is sick.
什么意思
What do you mean?
兔子病了
The rabbit's sick?
哪..哪种病
What... what kind of sick?
怎么..你给兽医打电话了吗
How... Did you call a vet?
你给她吃了多少百吉饼
How... how much bagel did you give her?
也没有很多 但是我的确跟你说过
Not that much but I just said that
它们就不能吃百吉饼
they're not supposed to have any bagel...
行 给我听着 尽快把问题解决了 明白吗
Okay. You know, what? Just... Just figure it out, okay?
打电话给我们的医生
Just call our doctor.
但是医生医的是人吧
But the doctor does people?
是 能医人 当然也能医兔子
Yeah, if he can do people, he can do rabbits.
格丽   -别吵
-Gerri? -No.
你好 顺便一问
Hi, by the way.
这是在谈工作还是谈朋友呢
-Is this business or friendly? -
抱歉 我只是..   -那啥 卡洛丽娜
Not now.-Oh, sorry. I was just gonna ask... -Hey, Karolina?
你没问题吧 新闻稿写得怎么样了
How are you? How's the release coming?
等等快好了
-Almost.
谁去宣布呢
-And who's gonna announce?
我去   -我可以去
-I can do it. Oh... Well. -I'll do it.
好吧
oh well
是桑蒂
It's Sandi.
什么   -哪一个
-What? -Which one?
能说话那个
The one who can talk.
我接了
Yeah?
喂 桑蒂
Hey, Sandi?
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
好 你接着说
Well, go on.
行吧 但是
All right, but...
你认真的吗
Seriously?
好吧
Okay.
他们加了一个附带条件
So they have one more proviso.
他们想废除私人飞机
They want to take away the private jets.
私人飞机? 没门
The PJs? No.
那还用说 没门
Yeah. Well, duh. But no.
他们根本就是想羞辱他
That's just to try and humiliate him.
来真的吗 还是说 他们只是想再捞点好处
Well, was it... was it real or are they just basting the turkey?
我...我们同意了吧 爸
Let's just eat it, Dad,
过后你再让他们滚蛋
you can tell them to fuck off later.
对 我们可以提出限制个人使用或里程数
Yeah. We could just offer to...to cut personal use, or a mileage cap.
扯淡 没门 一开始他们要私人飞机 我没有抗议
Bullshit. No. First, they came for the PJs and I said nothing.
之后 他们就会要求巨额补偿款 你们明白吗
Then they come for the outsized compensation payments, you know?
这...不行 纯粹是扯淡 他们会让步的
This is... no, this is bullshit. They'll back down.
他们不会因为这个 就放弃交易
They're not gonna blow it up over this.
对不对
Right?
爸
Dad?
我要撒个尿
I need a piss.
-小西 -好 你要不要...
Shiv? Sure, do you need some help?
找人帮忙..我可以打电话...找...
Or I can con... reach out to...
你来
You.
走吧
Let's go.
别动
Stay.
你..想现在做决定吗
You wanna make a decision now,
在你去之前 还是
before, or...
爸
Dad?
-Dad?
卡尔   -什么
-Karl? -What?
弗兰克准备让你上台了
-Frank's about to introduce you.
我...我说什么  老板..
I... I what do I say? Boss?
我...我...
What... what do...
好吧 那什么..
Okay.
斯图伊不接电话
Well, Stewy's not picking up.
卡尔现场发挥
Karl, vamp!
真棒 卡尔即兴演讲   -你做得到的 加油
Great. Karl vamping. You got it, man!
那么 闲话少叙
So without further ado
让我们有请财务总监 卡尔·马勒
and with interesting things to tell you,
相信 他会给大家带来
I believe please welcome our Chief Financial Officer,
精彩的发言
Karl Muller.
说慢点 交易可能要黄
Slow down, the deal may be off.
我..还有其他事要处理
I... I'm needed elsewhere,
所以
so...
你即兴吧
Vamp.
祝你好运 弗兰克
Bon chance, Franco.
真棒
Excellent!
天大的好消息
Wonderful news!
好的 实际上我们得
Well, in fact, we will be
晚一点再听财务总监的发言 在此之前
hearing from our Chief Financial Officer a little later, and before that
不妨再听我 多劳叻两句话
a little further ado.
其实 应该说是 很多句话
In fact, much ado.
关于某些事情的具体情况
Much ado about, something.
洛根
Logan.
洛根 我们等不了了
Logan, we can't wait any longer.
我们怎么回复   -对啊 爸 我们怎么办
-What do we say? -Yeah. What's it gonna be, Dad?
我们需要你给个答案
We need an answer.
你怎么想的 洛根 同意还是不同意
What do you think, Logan? Yes or no?
让他们滚
fuck 'em.
我
I...
让他们滚
fuck 'em!
爸 你确定
You sure, Dad? That...
你确定要这么做
Are you sure you wanna do this?
我...
I...
爸你没事吧 你是知道什么吗..
You okay, Dad? Do you... do you know something, or...
我是说这个决定影响巨大
I mean, that is...this is a huge call.
我们能接受吗
Are we happy?
药
Pills.
我刚给过你 先生 你还需要其他的吗
I just gave you some, sir. You need something else?
泰诺
Tylenol?
他还好吗 我是说 他的反应是正常的吗 他没出什么问题吧
Is he okay? I mean, does this make sense? -Is he... is he okay?
当然 一切正常 他屁事没有
-Yeah. Yes, it makes sense he's fucking okay.
他拿整个公司做赌注 因为他巨他娘的牛逼
Look, he's gambling the company because he's a fucking badass.
他知道自己在做什么  -他..
He knows what he's doing.
他确实暂钉截铁地拒绝了 是不是
Was that a... that was a... that was a clear no, right?
他非常明确地拒绝了 不接受
He definitely said fucking no, no deal.
是吗   -肯定是的
-Did he? -That was a definite no.
对 如果我们不跟他们交易
Yeah. I mean, if we win
就赢了投票那就什么都不用损失了
without a deal, then it's all upside.
我们现在真的要赌吗
We're really rolling the dice here?
这是老爸的经典作风
This is classic-fucking-Dad.
要是我们撑过来了 这件事可以载入史册
I mean, if we do come through, it is one for the memoirs.
这真的太刺激了
I mean, it really is quite thrilling.
这就是一场豪赌啊 怎么能这样
It's a huge fucking gamble! -For what?
他一直相信自己的胆识 而且从没失过手
-He's trusted his gut before and it's always worked out.
天哪 我要是知道他想什么就好了
Oh, God, I wish I know the thinking.
不过 确实他之前也遇到过这种情况 所以.
But, yeah, I mean, he has been here before, so.
他确实在去卫生间路上接了个电话
He did get a call on the way to the restroom.
你他妈怎么不早说
-You could have fucking mentioned.
好的 那他可能知道点什么
-Okay. So maybe he knows something?
他永远都知道点什么 他可是老爸啊
Well, he always knows something. It's fucking Dad.
他未卜先知 料事如神
He's six moves ahead.
好吧
Okay.
所以 我们真的要这么做吗
Well, so we're really fucking doing this?
叫他们滚蛋
fuck 'em.
那好吧 叫他们滚蛋
Okay, fine. -fuck 'em.
滚蛋 那我
I'll... -fuck 'em.
来打电话吧
I'll make the... the "fuck 'em" call.
西沃恩   -喂 是这样.
Siobhan. Hey, so, no.
不接受你们不放宽专机的条件
Either you fold on the jets
我们就发起投票赌一把
or we'll take our chances on the vote?
他不会放宽专机这个条件的
Nope. He's not gonna fold on the jets.
那我们就投票吧
So we'll go to the vote.
真的吗 为什么
Seriously? Why?
不知道
I don't know.
我只是照我爸说的去做
I just do what my Dad tells me.
格雷格
Greg.
你是..在叫我吗
Did you say... did you say "Greg"?
把这个拿给弗兰克
Get this to Frank.
快去 他在台上 拿去给弗兰克
Now. He's on stage, get this to Frank now.
没问题
Okey dokey.
在对公司政策进行重大改革之后
And after a major overhaul of company policies
我们继续致力于 将邮轮打造得 既安全又独特
we continue to strive to make Cruises a safe and special place
并为我们的顾客带去特别的回忆
that provides special memories for all our customers.
成就光明的未来
It adds up to a bright future all around.
那
Well, that's...
靠 结束了
fuck, that's done.
很好 很果断 如果结束了
Good, decisive. I mean, if it's done,
如果我们能赢 那就很好
you know, if we win, that's good.
那边什么情况..
What's going on with the...
老家伙那边
the Raisin?
抱歉你是说..总统吗
I'm sorry with...-with the president?
我们能让雷文海德播报吗
-Can we get Ravenhead on the air?
你说现在吗 雷文海德
You mean now? Ravenhead
现在是日间节目   -打给米歇尔·安
-it's daytime programming? -Call Michelle Anne
让她找证券交易委员会 结束这场会议
tell her to get the SEC to shut this meeting down.
好 我们会处理的
Okay, well, we'll look into that.
我要撒个尿
I need to piss.
他人呢   -我吗 又是我
-Where is he? -Who? Me? Again?
当然 走
Yeah. Sure, okay.
好的
All right.
你们要去厕所吗
You guys off to the bathroom?
好的   -这边走
All right.
这他妈关你屁事
What fucking business is it of yours?
不 不 我只是..
Oh, no, no, I just...
只是...厕所在这后边
just making... yeah. I think it's just this back this way still.
我知道   -没事 他知道路
-It's good, I got it. -Okay, okay. He's got it.
好
Yes.
我们想花点时间
We'd like to take few moments now
给大家介绍一下我们的电视及电影板块
to talk to you about our TV and movie divisions
以及我们在内容创作方面的雄心壮志..
and our mighty ambitions for content creation and...
我不知道他们在想什么
Look, I don't know their thinking.  All right?
很..扯蛋
It's... its fucked.
真棒  你不应该是我的内应吗
Oh, great. You're supposed to be my inside fucking track.
当然 但飞机这茬是打哪来的
Well... Well, where did the plane bullshit come from?
真够小心眼的
Because that's petty.
我们的合作关系很复杂
We're a complicated coalition
桑迪是世上最狂躁的植物人
and Sandy's the angriest fucking vegetable.
好了 听着 我能力挽狂澜
All right. Listen, I can salvage this.
我正出发去找他们谈   -祝你好运
-I'm on my way to talk to them. -Good luck.
这个好战的绿皮西葫芦
But the fucking belligerent Zucchini here
毅然决然地要取消和解了
is set to close negotiations for good.
别急就...坚持住兄弟
Okay, just... just hang tight, dude.
傀儡大师出马了
Puppet master's on it.
洛根 你还好吗
Logan, you okay?
需要帮助吗
Need help?
你还好吗 老大
Hey, you okay, big man?
还好吗 有没有...被夹到
Are you okay? Did you get it... did you get it caught?
没有 帮我一把
No. Give me a hand.
行 不是...是要我..
Okay. Yeah. Not to...
要我帮你握着权杖吗   -不是
like you don't need to hold the scepter, too? No.
好的
Okay.
别急 慢慢来
Okay. Take your time.
慢慢来 不用急
Take your time, no rush. Yeah.
你还好吗 你直打哆索
Are you okay? You're really shivering.
我们最好带你去看医生
I think we need to get you seen by somebody.
我觉得..
I think...
谢谢你儿子
Thanks, son.
乐意效劳
Any time, Pop...
爸爸
Papa.
天哪
Oh, dear.
等等是米歇尔·安
Wait. It's Michelle Anne,
想跟你爸谈谈  说他不接电话
wants to talk to your dad   -says he's not picking up.
怎么 她又来抱怨报道的事吗
She's moaning about the coverage again?
她说事态紧急 所以.
She says it's urgent, I mean...
告诉她 我们会回电的
Tell her we'll call her back.
跟她说 要不是我们忙看对付司法部
Yeah. Tell her he'd have time to talk
我们就有空跟她聊聊了
if we weren't busy fighting the fucking DOJ.
你好 米歇尔·安
-Hi, Michelle Anne. -Hey.
乐意之至 我们会找到他的
Okay. Well, we're... we will...
随后会给你回电 小西
Hey, Shiv.
小西你爸完全迷糊了
Shiv, your dad is totally out of it.
什么
What?
爸 你还好吗   -小西来了
-Hey, Dad, are you okay? -No, no, don't get up, sir.
不 不 别起身   -别起来
-No, no, Marcia, Marcia. -Don't get up.
玛西娅 玛西娅
Marcia. Marcia.
什么
What?
现在不行 不行
Not now. Not now.
我得重新构思我的演讲
I have to rethink my speech
这需要时间
and it'll take me time.
我需要时间 谢谢你 玛西娅
So I need time. Thank you, Marcia.
-好的   -要命
Its OK  -fuck
这真是..  -怎么回事
Yeah its all  -What？
好
Okay.
各位...
Hey, everybody...
洛根现在有点不对劲
just to say that Logan is not really himself right now.
凯莉
-Hey, Kerry.
我爸在吃什么药吗
Is dad on any medication?
他患了尿路感染 他怎么了
He has UTI. Why? Is he all right?
他的药会让他精神错乱吗
Could his meds make him confused?
不应该啊 他不吃药才会这样
Shouldn't. That's what happens if he doesn't take them.
他身上带药了吗 在哪呢
Okay. Does he have them? Where are they?
不...我把药留给他了 .
But... I'm not... I left them with him
我马上过去
but, I'm gonna... I'm gonna be right there.
我带药剂了 我给他医生打电话
I have shots and I'm calling his doctor.
好的
Okay.
他得了尿路感染
Dad's got a fucking UTI.
什么 真的吗 那不是
What? Seriously? Well, is that...
那应该不是很严重吧
I mean, no, it's not that fucking serious, right?
什么 这把年纪得这病就是要命
What? At his age? That could make you crazy.
里根得了这玩意 差点往比利时发射核弹
Reagan had one and nearly nuked Belgium.
我操 什么
fuck. What?
他这样... 他这样多久了
How long has he... how long has he been like this?
他说不的时候 也这样吗
Was he like this when he said no?
他可是让整个公司都命悬一线了
When he risked the whole company?
这事不许外传
No one hears about this.
照顾好他
Go look after him.
汤姆...汤姆
Tom. Tom.
快去   -好的
Come on, go...
我们怎么办 他得了尿路感染
-What do we do? He has a UTI.
尿路感染   -得叫医生过来
-UTI? Yeah. Somebody has to call a doctor.
我们不能给他喝点红莓汁
Can we just give him some cranberry juice
然后再问问那交易怎么办
-and ask him about the deal again?
他刚才在找卡洛琳
-Just asking for Caroline.
我靠 他完全疯了
Oh, fuck, he's piss-mad.
不  但他答应把欧洲有线电视板块交给我的时候
You know, but he was... he was in really good shape
状态可好了
when he offered me European cable.
他什么时候说的
When did he say that?
因为那会儿 他一定已经疯了
Because he was definitely out of it -when he said that.
不 他当时逻辑清晰
-No he was cogent at that point.
我向你保证 绝对不是
-I can guarantee you he wasn't.
听起来他已经失心疯好一段时间了
It sounds like he's been out of it for a while.
不 我们其实并不知道
Okay, no, no, we don't actually know that, okay?
他接的那通电话是什么
What about the phone call he took?
或许他做的决定才是正确的
Maybe the decision he made is the right decision
我们又不知道他多久开始犯的迷糊
and we actually don't know when he went piss-mad.
那电话也说不好是谁
That? No, that could have been anything.
可能是自动语音推销 或他的泌尿科医生   -是啊
That could have been Robocall or fucking urologist?
不 我估计他已经疯了好一会儿了
No, no, I suspect that he's been piss-mad for quite a while.
真的吗 你这位专管撒尿的大侦探波洛
Oh, oh, do you? The fucking Hercule Poirot of fucking piss over here.
小西 你要...推翻他的决定吗
Shiv, do you... Should you overrule him?
回去找桑迪和斯图伊 说我们改主意了
Go back to Sandy and Stewy and say we've changed our minds?
是啊 我也觉得 你该这么做
Yeah, I think you should totally do that.
老爸“最想“看到这样了 去吧 推翻他的决定
-Dad loves that kind of thing. -Well... Look at him.
不 不能 不能这样
Yeah  no , cant do that
各位 他说 他还是要上台演讲
Guys, he... he says he still needs to make his speech.
你们觉得呢   -他还能演讲吗
-What... what do you think? -Can he do the speech?
他..他能...   他能演讲吗
-Can... Can he? -"Can he do the speech?"
这位精神错乱的英格兰疯王
the demented fucking piss-mad, king of England?
他什么都可能说出
He could say anything,
他有可能会说 自己是芭芭拉·史翠珊
he could tell everyone he's Barbra Streisand.
算了 我们还是放弃吧
No, I think we have to... we have to drop it, right?
但至少 他得上台
No. But at the very least, he should be on stage.
让他出现一下 效果会很好
It would be great to get the body up there.
我们尽量拖延他上台的时间
Okay, we push it as late as we can
或者 只让他上台就够了
and maybe if we just get him on stage that'll be enough.
没错 我们用暗门 把他送上去
Oh, yeah, sure. Maybe send him up through a trap door
然后再加点干冰效果
surrounded by dry ice.
医生人呢
Where is this doctor anyway?
他..他很介意椅子底下有只死猫
He's... he's concerned there is a dead cat under his chair.
真是好消息  -椅子下面有东西吗
Oh, great. Okay. -Is there anything under the chair?
不   -格雷格..
-Greg.
很好   -拿给弗兰克
-No. -Oh, okay, great, get that to Frank.
他似乎很坚持 而且....
Yeah. He seems insistent and he says that
他还说 他不想让罗丝看到
he doesn't want Rose to see it
他要科林去把它拿出来
and he wants Colin to take it out.
好啊 让科林去拿出来
Fine, have Colin take it out.
好的   -很好 谢谢雨果 谢谢你
-Okay. -Good. Thanks... Hugo. Thank you.
医生在路上了
-The doctor's on his way.
你他妈的 之前怎么不提这事
Why the fuck didn't you mention this before, huh?
他不想让任何人知道
He didn't want anyone to know.
好啊 结果还真不错呢
Okay. Well, it's worked out well, hasn't it?
我操
Oh, fuck.
太棒了 是谁邀请你来的 谢谢
Oh, great. Hey, who invited you? Thanks.
到底是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
没事 尽在我们掌握   -他要搞砸这笔交易
-It's fine. We got it under control. -He's squashing the deal?
我们能行 你们现在必须改主意
You have to turn this around, right now.
是的,   -我们能控制住局面 好吗
-We got this under control. Okay?
我们正在想办法
-Yeah. Yeah. We're figuring it out.
多谢关心
Thank you for your concern.
怎..怎么回事
What... what's happening?
他的医生马上来   -他妈的到底怎么回事
-The doctor's on the way. -What the fuck is going on?
没事 没什么
It's fine. It's all right.
那是什么 请你离开好吗
-What is that? -Will you leave, please?
那是一只 想象中的猫 你现在能滚蛋吗
That is an imaginary cat. Now could you please fuck off?
仔细听我说
-Listen to me very carefully.
好的   -你们所有人
-Okay. All of you.
你们正在把公司拱手让人
This is you throwing it away.
你们以为他们在虚张声势吗 大错特错
You think they're bluffing? They are not fucking bluffing
你们让我呕心沥血奋斗所得的一切
and you're putting everything I have fought and bled for
命悬一线 而我不会允许这种事发生
on the fucking edge and I am not gonna let that happen
你们听明白了吗   -明白
-do you understand me? -Yes.
这里不欢迎你   -你们给我解决好
-You're not welcome here. -You fix it.
你们他妈的给我解决这事
You fucking fix it.
你可以走了 你可以离开了
-You may go. You are excused.
这里不欢迎你 你无权出现在这里
-You're not welcome. You have no right to be here.
请离开   -多谢你的关心
Thank you very much for your concern.
请离开 谢谢
Please. Thank you.
快滚 幻想症
Go, delusional.
幻想症患者正走出这间房
fucking delusional man leaving the room right now!
你们最好赶快叫医生 不然我就叫我的来
-And figure out a fucking doctor... or Im calling mine
快滚出这里   -多谢你的关心
-Get the fuck out of here. -Thank you so much for your concern
说得好像你很在乎一样
like you give a fuck.
搞不好 是你给他吃了什么 普京 操
You probably slipped him something, Putin. fuck!
爸
-Dad.
让弗兰克留在台上,   -弗兰克为什么这么生气
-Keep Frank on stage. -Why is Frank so angry?
刚刚那是肯德你   -弗兰克不高兴了吗
-Oh, that's Kendall. -Go... Is Frank... is Frank upset?
不 有人对弗兰克发火
-Hey, Dad, no. -No. Some people were nasty to Frank
-不过现在没事了,   -非常生气 有人在大吼大叫
-and it's fine now though. -Very mad, people are yelling.
谁对他不好   -不不不 你快坐下
-Who... who was nasty? -No, no, you sit down
别担心 他没事的  -没人可以...
-don't worry, he's okay. -Relax, Logan.
只有我才能对他不好
I'm the only one who's allowed to be nasty to him
不 之前有些蠢人 现在已经走了
nobody else can be nasty to Frank.
该死
Shit
我们会携手合作
And we will all work together as a team
带领公司走向更光辉的未来
to lead the company to a brighter future.
现在 有请格丽·吉你曼 我们的临时首席执行官
And now I will hand you over to Gerri Kellman our interim CEO.
该死的儒夫
You cowardly prick.
谢谢 弗兰克
Thank you, Frank.
首先 我想回顾一下
I'd like to begin by reflecting
我在韦斯达工作三十年来
on some of the many changes
看到的一些变化
I have seen in my 30 years at Waystar.
他在挂点滴 补充水分了
He's on fluids and hydrating
应该很快就会好
-so it should be pretty quick.
他应该没问题吧
-He's definitely gonna be okay?
不过 要多久
-But how quick?
他又不是方便面 一下就能好
-Well...-He's not a cup of instant noodles.
当然 但我们能加快速度吗
-Sure, but can we speed it up
像是给他输血或是打一针肾上腺素
like a blood bag or an adrenaline shot?
天啊冷静点
Jesus, fucking take it easy.
你想给他塞辣酱栓剂吗
You wanna give him the fucking Tabasco suppository?
去你的 这是他会希望看到的
fuck you, it's what he'd want.
我才去你的 重点是 我们要照顾他 好吗
Yeah. But the main things is that we look after him. Okay?
是啊 很显然 我也赞同这点 罗曼
Yeah. Well, obviously, I agree, Roman.
是吗 真的吗
Oh, yeah? Really?
因为听起来 你想像发动皮卡车一样
Because it sounded like you want to jumpstart our father
来唤醒我们父亲
like he's a fucking pickup truck.
该死 你们—会儿联系我吧
Oh, shit. Can you like call me when he's less scary?
太吓人了
Scary
积极的方向
Positive direction.
我们会为邮轮部门寻找可能性
We will explore alternatives for our cruise division
也可能转让它的所有权
including a possible divestiture.
并且 我们会启动股票回购计划
And we'll initiate share repurchase plan
特殊股息  我们还在创建
and a special dividend. -And we'll be forming...
医生说他会没事的 但我不知道
-Doctor says he's gonna be fine -but, I don't know.
没事的 他睡着了,   -由我们富有远见的
-It's fine, he's... he's asleep.  -to be spearheaded by...
首席运营官 罗曼·罗伊 所引领
...our visionary chief operating officer Roman Roy.
喂 是的 是的
Hey, Lia, yeah,
我想问..在你看来
I was... I was wondering just, in your view, do you...
你觉得 有没有可能起诉
Do you think it's possible to sue a person
比方说 一个人的祖父母
a grandparent, for example
以一种
in a way which is like...
看起来像是充满爱意的方式
like in an affectionate way?
能不能传达
That might... that might convey
我爱你  我很庆幸你能出现在我生命中
like "I love you and I... I'm glad you're part of my life
但我要对你采取法律行动  类似的含义
but I am taking legal action against you"?
我们要...   -这不能
-We're getting just... -This isn't...
这不能拉动任何摇摆投票
this isn't turning any floating votes our way.
我们要不要打电话说 有炸弹危险
Should we call in a bomb threat?
他的呻吟越来越大声了
So his moaning's getting louder.
不过 他能上台吗
Okay, but can he do that on stage?
坐着轮椅上挥手吗   -该死 我们不能
Is it a wheel on and wave? fuck. Like we're not
让发疯的熊 随该死的牛鞭起舞
gonna make the piss-mad bear dance with fucking cattle prods.
我们得照顾他 好吗
We need to be looking after him, okay?
就是说 他不演讲了吗
So he's not gonna do his speech?
那...那他现在...能说话吗
Well...-Is... is he... talking?
就这么决定了 我们就这样...
-Is that it though? Do we just...
就...我们就这样摆烂
does that... we go down
然后直接他妈的放弃吗
and get fucking give up?
不   -不是的
-No. -No.
玛雅
Maya,
说说你的看法
talk to me.
快点
Come on.
我强烈建议你们尽力和解
I strongly urge you to do whatever you can to settle.
好吧 我认为我们该回去找桑迪和斯图伊
Okay. I think we go back to Sandy and Stewy
试着挽救这笔交易 -是的
to try and save the deal.
不 你不能这么做 因为爸说了不和解
No, no, you can't because Dad said no deal.
不 爸没这么说 罗曼   -爸说了不和解
-Well, dad didn't say shit, Rome. -Dad said no deal!
不 他没说 尿道控制了他的大脑
No, he didn't. His urethra had wrested control from his brain.
至少 我去和他们谈谈 好吗
I at least talk to them, right?
好的   -好
-Right. -Yeah.
因为 如果投票 很可能.
Because if we go to the vote, we probably...
我们会输 卡尔
we lose. Karl?
弗兰克   -同意
-Frank?
汤姆 同意吗   -同意
Tom? Yes? Okay.
我同意   -好的 小罗你同意吗
-Yes. Yes. I say yes. Rome? You back this?
去吧 去搞砸这一切吧 蠢货
Go on. Yeah. Go fuck it up, moron.
我想请问 我们能否再谈谈
Hey, I was wondering if we could have another chat
就我们两个人 在投票结束前
just the two of us before the vote closes.
感谢你们的支持
Thank you for your support.
这就是韦斯达的力量
This is the power of Waystar.
一个崭新的开始 但旅程依旧
A bright new beginning, but the journey remains the same.
我们在韦斯达·罗伊科..
We at Waystar Royco...
她没话可说了 实在不行了
She dried out, just couldn't do it.
她播了视频 但我们得结束投票了
She hit the video but we have to close this vote.
只能这样了
This is it.
白宫打来电话
I've got the White House on the line. So...
是啊 自从泛美网科改变主意后
Yeah, they've been coming at us from all sides
他们就开始全面针对我们
since the ATN pivot.
不是米歇尔·安  是总统打来的
It's not Michelle Anne, it's the president.
他希望进行一次紧急会谈
He wants an urgent conversation.
通过那部手机吗 现在
On... On that phone now?
是的 现在是静音 但现在在总机上
Yeah. I mean, on mute, but it's a switchboard.
他要找洛根
He wants Logan.
好吧 不过现在不是谈话的最佳时机
Right. Well, that's not ideal.
我们能拒绝吗
I mean, can we... can we just say no?
你们觉得 如果我们现在
Well, how do we feel about
拒绝总统的话 会怎样
saying no to the president right now?
我很想拒绝总统
Oh, I would love to say no to the president.
我是说 他也没法跟爸通话
I mean, he can't talk to dad.
我们能不能就让他滚蛋
Can we just tell him to fuck off?
反正他明天就不记得了
I mean, by all accounts he won't remember by tomorrow.
是的 但我想 会不会和
Yeah, I was wondering if it might be
司法部的事有关
about the DOJ and everything.
已经太晚了 不过...
I mean, it's fucking late, but...
如果调查压力降低了 我们可以把这事透露出去
if the pressure got turned down and we can leak it
然后我们可以让格丽重回台上
and then we throw Gerri back up on stage
继续说话 拖时间   -我来接吧
-and just keep her talking? -I could do it.
还是别了
I think, no.
我想或许该由小西接 能让小西回来吗 弗兰克
I think maybe Shiv. Shiv. Can we get Shiv back, Frank?
格丽
Gerri, Gerri,
格丽 我们得找个人.
hey, Gerri, we need someone...
格丽 我们得找个靠谱的人 和..
Gerri, we need someone sensible to talk
和总统现在通话   -我来接吧
-to the president right now... -I can do it.
谈一件要紧的 私人事件
...on an urgent personal matter.
罗曼 你见过他的 对吧   -这个嘛..如果..抱歉
Roman, you've met him. right? -Well... well,  If it's between...
只能在罗曼和格丽之间做选择 我绝对会.
sorry, Roman and Gerri I would definitely...
我来和他谈 小贱人
I'll talk to him a little bitch, here
能快点决定吗 因为这事挺急的
Should we hurry? Because I...-I think it's kind of urgent.
我接是可以接 但是
-I mean, I can do it but,
罗曼 你和他们关系更好 对吧
Roman, you get along with them, right?
这里最有洛根那个范儿的 就是
I mean, if anyone here is bootleg Logan...
罗曼...
Roman.
行吧 给我
Yeah, okay, gimme.
就说你很尊重他 可以帮他传话
Just explain, it's out of respect and you can take the message.
懂了 懂了 不过是总统而已 没事
Yeah, yeah, I got it. It's just the president, it's fine.
就他 这个有妥瑞氏症的小屁孩儿  你确定吗
This guy? Tony Tourettes? Are you kidding, are you sure?
不许爆粗口   -是吗
-Don't swear at him. -Oh, really?
让总统给我吹萧 难道不酷吗
It's not cool to tell the president to blow me?
你好 总统先生 我是..抱歉
Hey, Mr. President. This... sorry...
对我..
Yeah. No.
您讲 您讲
Crosstalk, you go.
不 我是...我是他的儿子 罗曼
Yeah. No, this is actually... I'm his son, Roman.
对 就是那个
Yup. That one.
父亲现在不方便讲话 不过..
Look, he can't talk right now but...
你还好吗
how you doing?
好的 我一定把你的怒意转达给他
Yeah. I will certainly let him know that you are upset.
我还得赶回去照顾我爸 说吧 什么事
Hey, I can't leave my dad alone. So what's going on?
是这样
Look,
考虑再三
upon further reflection
我们决定接纳你的筹码
we have decided to accept your counter.
我们可以交出专机   -真好..
-We can eat the jets. -Okay.
附加条件是... -没有附加条件
-Any context? -No.
经过一番深思熟虑
We just... we took another look and thought
我们觉得 这才是最好的出路
that this was the clearest way forward.
你爸也这么想吗
And this is what your dad wants?
没错 我爸就是这么想的
Yeah. It is what my dad wants.
很好 这样很好
Well... well, good, this is good.
真棒 那就解决了吧
Great. So we're good?
或者 没有问题了吧
We're, you know, we're going to be good?
当然
Sure.
不过 按照我爸的性格
Well, honestly, knowing where my dad is coming from
我怀疑他还有别的想法
I do just wonder if there will be one more thing.
别关机 再联系
So don't turn your phone off.
不是  我说
Okay, come on, look.
我们俩就不能把这事敲定吗
Is there something that we can work out here?
你懂的  事不宜迟
-You know, it's now or never.
我不确定
-I... I don't know.
桑蒂  我
Sandi, look I...
我觉得 你爸在这件事中
I don't think it's right how
不应该把你边缘化
your dad sidelines you in all this.
而且 我也希望董事会里
And maybe it's appropriate...
有一个人和我志同道合
for me to have somebody likeminded on the board.
你觉得
So how about...
董事会第四席
a fourth seat...
给你...
on the board
怎么样
for you?
你可以说 是你逼我们交出了这个席位
You can tell him that you screwed it out of us
把我爸气得差点一命鸣呼
and my dad was losing his shit and it nearly killed him.
四个席位   -没错
-Four seats, that's... -Yeah.
四个席位可不少了  他会满意的
That's a lot of seats, he will like that.
没错   -对
-Yeah. -Yeah.
比原来的三个席位多了一个
Well, it's... it is one more than three by my count
那为了平衡  韦斯达也得多一个
so Waystar for balance, we'll need an extra one.
给我
For me.
我懂了
I see.
这个我爸应该不会满意
Yeah, he won't love that.
你就告诉他.
Okay. Well, look, just tell him that the fucking...
放心吧 这市场永远不可能
the markets will never
让我和我兄弟做首席执行官
let me or my brothers be CEO.
这话说出来你自己信吗
Oh, come on, do you believe that?
我只关心你爸信不信
I just care if your dad believes it.
我得走了
Look I should go.
看我能不能说动他吧
See if I can sell it.
不过 这个 洛根没意见吧
But this is... this is good with Logan?
我能说服我爸
I can sell it.
你能说服你爸吗
Can you sell it?
好的 我会转达
Well, I will relay that.
你不会再参选 他希望我们这下满意了
You are not running again and he hopes that we are happy.
不行 我们需要内线
-No! -We need access!
请问 这事已经板上钉钉了吗
And I mean, and that's decided already?
因为 我觉得
Because, you know, I think that
不管我们有什么小小分歧
whatever our... our minor difference is
我们都希望你能施以援手
we would urge you to... to not stand aside.
不 我很高兴能做你们的传话人
Yup. But, no, I will be the messenger boy, happy to be that.
我只是觉得...没错
I just think... yeah.
我们的立场是这样 我是代表我父亲说的
I just think that our position and speaking for my father here.
我的立场是 好朋友之间是可以
You know, good friends can be really tough
说一些逆耳忠言的 但是呢
with their constructive criticisms
我们只是觉得
but we would just say, you know
觉得你是个
and I think that you are
是个足以载入史册的人物
a really significant historical figure
还可以成就更大的事业
who has a lot more to give.
没错 泛美全集团的人都会团结起来
Yeah. Well, the whole family at ATN could rally round
若失去你 可真是太遗憾了 先生 所以..
it would be a shame you know, sir, to lose you. So,
当然
absolutely.
好吧 这样的话 总统先生
Well, in that case, Mr. President
很荣幸能有这样的机会 是的
it has been a privilege to have the opportunity. Yeah.
祝你好...运 已经挂了
Best of luck to you and okay.
行吧
All right.  So...
他就是告诉我们一声
Yeah, he just wanted to
他不会再参选了
let us know that he's not gonna run again
他退出了   -真他妈的
-he's pulling out. -fuck and fuck.
没错 他的神经质问题
Yeah. Hey, his minor neurological issue
他觉得 以我们为首的媒体
which, you know the media starting with us,
说得太过了
have blown way out of proportion
他不想他的妻儿还有家人
and he doesn't want to put his wife and kids and family
也成为興论的焦点
through all the blah, blah, blah
然后他还骂了我爸和我
and fuck dad, and fuck me.
骂了泛美 骂了雷文海德
And fuck ATN and Ravenhead
还说 不管下一任总统是谁
and good luck getting the kind of access that he granted
预祝我们能继续享受红利
with whoever is the next president.
至于下任总统 照他的话说 会是只弱鸡
Which if left up to him  could be a chicken.
我去   -没错
fuck. -Yeah.
太糟心了
-Shit.
太棒了 真爽啊   -可不是吗 康纳
-Boom-shaka-laka. Hell, yeah. -fuck, yeah, Connor.
我觉得 我们失去了最强有力的盟友
I think we just alienated our most powerful ally.
的确 我们有了傀儡替我们掌控整个美国
I mean, it's kind of nice to know that we can like
这是个大好事 但是吧..
puppet master the whole American Republican project and all, but...
小西
Shiv...
四个席位
four seats.
什么   -我们交出专机
-What? -We eat the PJ's...
我们又多了一个席位
We get a seat! We get a seat!
对 这确实很难办 但是.
Yeah, that was pretty hard to finesse, but...
桑迪和他女儿桑蒂确定是
Sandy and Sandi are definitely...
同意交易了
-in, so...
格丽这样可以吗   -四个席位吗
Gerri, are we good?  Four seats.
太棒了
Oh, fuck,
这个当然得同意了
I would like to say yes to that.
我觉得
I just... I...
我觉得 我们应该同意 格丽
I think we need to say yes to that, Gerri.
我说 老爸随时都会
Can I just... at some point,
从那里走出来的 大家
dad is gonna walk out of there, so...
成交吗
Are we good?
我...我们....
I...We...
成交吗
Are we good?
四个席位交出专机
Four seats, no PJ's.
成交 成交 不投票 暂缓投票
We're good, we're good. Yeah. No vote, hold the voting.
好的 成交   -太棒了
-Okay, we're good. -Yes.
他们同意了 很认可这个结果
They're good, it's a yes from this end. So...
-真好-我们很满意
-Okay... We're good.
他们也同意了 成交
-Okay. They're good if we're good. -It's done.
太棒了    -那个
-Great. Great. Okay.
现在 我们得联系律师
So, we need to check the lawyers
让律师加入新内容 然后签字
they need to plug in a new detail and get signatures
然后和股东们说这件事
and then we can talk to the shareholders.
弗兰克 你已经付出很多了
Right, well, Frank, you've done so much already.
这次就让我来吧   -好吧
I would... I would be happy to do it.  I see
那 我们发布一篇新闻稿
Okay. So, we will publish a press release as... -Karl?
以卡尔的名义 对
as Karl  -As he's announcing. Exactly.
大功臣来啦
fucking superhero!
简直是惊人之举
The world's on fire.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Thank you. Thanks, honey.
今晚想去酒店开个房间吗
Hey, you wanna get a hotel room tonight?
酒店吗 不过...   -什么
-Hotel? I think there's... -Yeah.
家里还有好几个房间没好好待过
rooms in the apartment that we've never fully walked into.
但我觉得 在酒店房间里你的味道
I think there's just something about the way you... smell
还有你的身体都别具一番风味
the way your body looks at the time of the month.
你知道的 我就是你的舔狗   -什么时候
You know, I'm like a dog. What time?
·什么时候   -我想想我想想
Time of the... I think
我在你的生育期最沉渴
I'm just most horny when you're most fertile
这就是本能吧 对吧
you know, that's how it works, right?
这是
Is this,
汤姆 所以你才问我经期是什么时候吗
Tom, why you ask me when my period was?
当然不是   -你是在算日子吗
-No! No. -Are you tracking me?
不  我们就像同处女生宿舍  经期都一致
We're like a sorority house, we're in sync.
我只是能感应到你的性感时段
I'm just... I'm just vibing your sexy window.
汤姆 你不会是在悄悄做记录吧
Tom, are you keeping a shadow log?
研究月相
Watching the phases of the moon
计算我最适合受精的时间
to see when...when I'm most breedable?
没有 我只是在备忘录记了一下
-No, I just...I... like, counted the days on my iCal.
我没那么变态   -我的天
-It's not creepy. -Oh, my God.
这么做 并没有什么目的
It's not creep... no, it's not, come on.
我只是..
I've got like...
还能经历六次排卵期做爱 我就要进监狱了
six more ovulation windows until all sex is prison sex.
我说了 我不喜欢那时间
I said I didn't like the timing.
我觉得那时间正好 九到十二个月
Well, I think the timing is good like nine to twelve months
也是我预期服刑的时长
is kind of what I'm hoping I might serve.
这个空档很好
I think it's a good slot.
什么  在你离开的时候让我怀孕
What? Put one in for when you're out?
不 不 只是这会让你..
No, no, it's, we keep you...
-让我什么 不那么寂寞 但..
-What? -...like not company, but...
小西 我是需要些慰籍
I might need something, Shiv.
不然这一切有什么意义
Okay. Otherwise what is the point of all this?
我们的未来又会怎样
Where are we heading?
汤姆 老娘他妈的才不想当你的孵化器.
Tom, I don't wanna be your fucking incubator for...
你在牢里
when you're in prison
做做引体  读读克瑙斯果德
doing chin ups and reading Knausgaards.
你说得很难听
You're making it sound horrible
这没那么糟  很不赖的
and it's not horrible, it's nice.
天啊   -这是件好事
-Oh, my gosh. -It's supposed to be nice.
操
fuck.
我该露面了  一直在这躲着
Yeah, I should be out there, you know. I'm hiding back here.
看起来像丧家犬
It makes me look like I'm losing
但其实我快赢了
when actually I'm winning.
你缺席..   -斯图伊说了
-Your very absence... -Plus, Stewy says
和解了 这就安全了
we have the deal  so it's safe.
你的缺席确实有一股力量
Your very absence has a certain power.
我觉得 缺席让我看起来像个孬种
I think my absence makes me look like a little bitch.
我们坚信此次动态行动计划
We believe this dynamic action plan
会让诸位再次对韦斯达充满信心
will restore full confidence in the Waystar brand
不论是客户还是员工
for both our consumers and our employees' life.
我们处理了历史遗留的系统问题
We've addressed systemic issues that affected us historically
我们宣誓 今后会继往开来
and we vow to do better moving forward.
因为在韦斯达 我们会关心妇女权益
Because at Waystar, we've always cared about women.
容我打断一下
Yes, may I just interrupt for just a moment.
我们非常开心地告诉大家
We are very, very pleased to report
我们与梅斯贝里资本和弗尼斯传媒集团
that a settlement has been reached
已经达成共识
with Maesbury Capital and Furness Media Groups
这将会..
which will...
谢谢大家 我们都很开心
Thank you. We're all... we're all overjoyed.
洛根·罗伊 本人非常想亲临现场
And Logan, Logan Roy, just desperately wanted to be here
和各位股东分享这重要的时刻
to address his shareholders at this very important time.
众所周知 他是注重细节的人
He's a details guy, my friends
他曾不遗余力 亲力亲为
and he's been working very hard on this
他会和他的股东保持紧密联系
and he will be, connecting with his shareholders.
妈的   -老天啊
-fuck me. -fuck off.
拦住他 啊踩爆他的蛋蛋 阻止他
fucking stop him. Step on his balls, stop him.
我们不能找人吗
Do we have a... a guy?
就是啊 可   -没有保安吗
Do we have security?
抱歉 打断一下 可以吗
Sorry, do you mind?
什么 你要干什么
What? What are you doing?
我来接手   -不行
I'll take it from here. No... Ken...
请站到一旁   -小肯 别这样
-Step aside, please. -Ken, don't do this. What...
感谢 卡尔.穆勒 朋友们
-Karl Muller, everyone. -Ken...
我们无能为力了
We can't... we can't do anything about this.
科林哪去了  我们不能对他动粗
-Where's Colin? -We can't manhandle him.
科林在   -真不行吗
Colin is with...-Can't we?
科林在陪爸 在洛根那
-Colin's with Pop. He's with Logan.
大家知道 今天我其实
You know, I'm... I'm not actually...
没有被安排上台讲话
I'm not actually scheduled to speak today.
我只想说
I would like to say this.
我希望各位
I'd like to ask you all
能同我一道..
to please join with me
深深默哀....
in a moment of silence
悼念我们监管下牺牲的受害者
for all the victims of crimes that took place on our watch.
凯拉·梅森
-Kira Mason.
我的天啊
-Oh, my God.
关掉他的麦   -他好讨厌
Cut his mic... -He's so annoying.
你就管不住嘴   -自恋
The narcissism of this fucking guy.
这个狗逼   -他现在看起来疯了
You know what, he looks crazy
我觉得对我们来说是件好事
and I think that can be good for us.
艾丽斯·维斯普契
Iris Versppuci.
凯莉?罗
Kelly Robin...
凯莉....
Kelly...
凯莉·罗宾逊   -凯利斯
Kelly Robinson-Kellis.
他们关麦了吗..   -关了
Did... did they cut... Yes.
关了 但我还能听见 他嗓门真他娘的大
-Okay. No... But I can still hear... -Oh, shit. -Yeah. Because he's loud as fuck.
我们还能听见 把麦全关了
We can still hear him. Cut all mics, please.
他连领带都不打
He's not even wearing a tie.
我想宣布 我要发起一个基金会
I would just like to announce that I am launching a foundation
以纪念牺牲在我家族企业下的
in the name of victims who suffered sexual abuse
性受害者
in the hands of my family's company.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
我们早该砍掉他的
We should've chopped him down.
也是 不过
Yeah. Well,
这样会引人生疑
I guess it might've seemed suspicious.
像是把人当文件销毁
Kind of like shredding a human document.
四个席位
Four seats
又失去总统支持
and the Raisin gone.
司法部要是卷土重来怎么办
What if we get a more aggressive DOJ?
您好点了吗
You feeling better?
我在想 欧洲有线电视
So here I was thinking about European Cable
结果芝麻开门
and then boom, open sesame.
你们敢信吗
Can you believe it?
的确难以置信   -对啊
-It is hard to believe. -Yeah.
祝你顺利   -谢谢
-Have a good time. -Thank you.
我还有些进展
Yeah. So I got... I have a little bit of... of a development.
显然 我在尤恩活着的时候不能控告他
Apparently, I can't technically sue Ewan while he's still alive.
但是我能告“绿色和平
But I can sue Greenpeace.
你要告“绿色和平
You're going to sue Greenpeace?
我喜欢你的作风  格雷格
I like your style, Greg.
那你下一个目标会是什么呢
Who do you think you're gonna go after next?
儿童救助基金会吗
Save The Children?
打断一下 各位
Sorry, everyone.
今日参加
I think...
股东大会的朋友们都同意
every attendee of today's shareholder meeting can agree
今天我已经讲得够多了
we've heard more than enough out of me today.
但是 我必须要说 大家做得很棒
But I just wanna say well done to all
洛根 小西
well done to Logan, well done to Shiv
今天孤注一逆风翻盘
on one hell of a Hail Mary.
敬大家
To us.
恭喜 老爸 成了
So, congratulations, you did it.
我需要知晓一下沟通细节
I need to see all the detail.
爸 细节没有问题
Dad, the detail is good.
席位是唯一办法
The seat was the only way.
吃亏的那一方 总是利用这个借口
Well, that's what people on the shitty end of a deal always say.
四席啊
Four seats.
但我说了 我们得保障一席
But I stipulated that we need a seat of our own
我们之前谈过的 不是吗
and that we talked about that, right?
董事会中再加一人 比如我
Adding another person to the board like me
或者康纳 谁都行
or Connor you know, whoever.
我们不能冒险投票
We couldn't risk a vote.
爸你那时不在岗位
You were... Dad, you were AWOL.
换作你..会怎么做
What would... what would you have done then?
反正不会那样做
Not that.
好吧 那你会怎么做呢
-Okay, but what would you have done?
我会想出办法
-I'd have figured it out.
该来想想后续行动了
Time to think on next moves.
你不想先品味这一刻吗
Don't you wanna just savor this moment for a minute
庆祝我们幸存下来
to, you know, that we came out of this alive?
水中有血 鲨鱼要来了
There's blood in the water, the sharks are coming.
我们得尽快进行收购
-We should hustle on acquisition.
就喝一杯庆祝下吧
-Just take this for a toast. Yeah.
老天
Oh, God.
小西 我在跟格丽讲重要的事情
Shiv, I'm trying to talk to Gerri about something important.
别他妈在我耳边逼逼了
Stop buzzing in my fucking ear!
看来有人满血复活了
Well, someone is feeling better.
敬各位
Here's to us.
敬大家
To us.
来宝贝
Hey, come here.
别这样 我又不是要让你怀孕
-I'm just... -Come on, I'm not gonna...I'm not gonna hump you.
抱一下 就抱一下
Just give you a hug. It's just a hug.
抱抱
Come on.
还好吧 爸爸
You okay? pop
小西太没眼力见了
Shiv being a bitch?
回应的话 都还挺正面的...
Responses, like, were kind of positive, actually.
你提到了基金会 这很好
It was good that you mentioned the foundation.
让整件事情私人化   -有什么反馈吗
-Yeah. First the feedback. -Personalize the whole thing.
有人评价说 是万豪檐下的布道
Someone called it, a sermon on the Marriott.
小肯..   -万豪檐下的布道
Ken...-Sermon on the Marriott?
我觉得可以当做流行语传开,   -好极了
-Yeah, I think that'll catch on. -That's going great.
打扰一下   -方向..正面吗
-In a... -I'm sorry. -...good way?
对了   -怎么了
Yeah. What's up? -Yeah.
你留一小会 可以吗
You mind sticking around for a little bit?
你爸有话对你说
Because I think your dad wants a word.
他有什么招
Yeah, what's... what's he got?
手指夹 还是皮革
The... brass knuckles or the bullwhip?
我准备了房间
-I have a room.
我被禁足了吗 凯莉
-Am I grounded, Kerry?
我只是准备了一间房    -好的走吧
-I have a room. -Yeah, let's go.
谁
Yeah.
小肯
-Hey, Ken.
怎么了
-Yeah.
我只想跟你说 你爸
I just wanted to tell you that your dad
他早走了所以...   -他走了吗
actually already left. So...Oh, he did?
好
Okay.
好 我去叫车
Okay, I'll call the car.
拉黑这个电话
Block this number for me.
你确定吗   -永久拉黑
-You sure? -Permanently.